# JUNWEN CHEN

0406 226 809 mayjunwenchen@gmail.com junwenchen.com



I'm a Full-Stack Developer and Interaction Designer.

I'm passionate about building empathy with people, and designing satisfying experiences for them. I enjoy development as it makes things happen and brings design to life.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### Designer & Front-end developer

JXT Global (Digital Agency) Aug 2017 - Dec 2017

## Full-Stack Developer

Pacific Magazines Feb 2018 - Now Worked closely with the design & front-end teams
Designed marketing materials (brochures/banners, etc)
Designed responsive websites with branding guidelines
Coded the website front-end with Javascript
Coded EDMs

Develop CMS/digital publishing/E-commerce platforms Work on both front-end(Javascript) and back-end(.Net/C#) Work in Agile & Scrum environment Conduct QA tasks

## **EDUCATION**

#### Master of Interaction Design

The University of Sydney
July 2016 - June 2018

## **Bachelor of Information Security**

China University of Mining and Technology Sept 2012 - June 2016 Designing solutions with user-centred methods Prototyping with programming languages Developed solid user research and design thinking skills

Gained solid knowledge on computer science basics Gained solid knowledge on programming fundamentals Developed strong problem solving and reasoning skills

# **SKILLS**

